

Phoenix, AZ **1** 520.389.3119 **4**

martha.g.moreno@hotmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/martha-gissela-moreno in

Software Developer in training focused on front-end and back-end development. Over 16 years of Technical Account & Project Management experience in the electronics and automotive manufacturing industry. Results oriented, self-driven, and versatile professional with highly developed analytical, problem solving and collaboration skills.

Skills Summary

	•		
Embedded Programming	Front-end	Back-end	<u>Others</u>
(Undergraduate)	HTML	(in-progress)	 Project Management
• C++	CSS	 MongoDB 	 Team Management
Java	 JavaScript 	 ExpressJS 	 Strategic Planning
 LabView 	 ReactJS 	 NodeJS 	 New Business Development
VHDL	 GitHub 		 Level-C Communication

Experience

APRIL 2007 - SEPTEMBER 2021

Global Account Manager / Henkel Corporation

Develop and manage execution of global strategic plans to exceed customer expectations and drive new worldwide business at top tier high technology accounts (Intel, HP) and Automotive OEMs (Stellantis). Manage a team of account managers and technical managers and lead cross-functional teams to secure the execution of new design programs and new product introductions.

MAY 2007 - APRIL 2014

Account Manager/ Channel Development Manager / 3M

Develop and lead engineering design and manufacturing process projects at top automotive, electronics. and industrial customers as part of a long-term solutions provider strategy. Manage and grow international tier-A Distribution partners to increase market share and gain new engineering specifications.

MAY 2005 - MAY 2007

Project & Academia Engineer / National Instruments

Provide technical advice and support to industrial and academic customers on software and test equipment. Create training, schedule and technical material for professors and researchers at nationally recognized Universities.

Education

AUGUST 2021-IN PROGRESS

Professional Certificate in Coding: Full Stack Development with MERN / MIT xPRO

DECEMBER 2009

Master of Science in Electrical Engineering / Universidad Autonoma de Ciudad Juarez

DECEMBER 2006

BS Digital Systems and Communications Engineering / Universidad Autonoma de Ciudad Juarez

Certifications

DECEMBER 2020

Project Management Professional (PMP) / Project Management Institute

JANUARY 2020

Negotiation Mastery / Harvard Business School Online

NOVEMBER 2019

Experienced Business Management Skills / IESE Business School